Davies Okpeta

Software Developer

Phone: 08118968777 Linkedn: @daviesOkpeta

E-mail: thenerfsenpai@gmail.com Github: @Nefario3k

A software developer with over **3years** of experience specializing in software development for websites, webapps and database structure and maintenance. I can implement seamless content management systems from managing estate housing to financial institutions. My greatest strength is team management, client engagement and dedication to task assigned to the team.

Experience

Dec 2020 - Feb 2021

Frontend Web Developer

Udemy

- Acquired skills and certifications relating to frontend web development.
- Built functional webapps and websites with beginner user-friendly UI designs using HTML, CSS, and vanilla JavaScript.
- Improved website performance by implementing search engine optimization techniques.

Feb 2022 - Present

Software Developer

Bex-it Digital Solutions

- Developed and maintained software applications using a variety of programming languages.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to ensure timely and successful project delivery.
- Improved the efficiency of the software development process through the implementation of automated testing and SOPs.
- Responsible for all content management system development.
- Responsible for team engagement for successful delivery.
- Client engagement for clear cut communication of specified goals and requirement for projects.

Education

August 2016 - September 2021

Bachelor of Science in Applied Mathematics

Federal University, Otuoke.

- Graduated summa cum laude.
- Created a system to calculate the effect of lipoprotein concentration on M.H.D blood flow through parallel plate with heat source and magnetic intensity.

Skills

Programming Languages – proficient in the basics of web development as well as JS frameworks.

Client management – proven track record of managing and clear communicating with clients with maximal support.

Project management – history of successful completed and satisfied client project delivered on or before an agreed upon time frame.

Software

Node.js

Php

Laravel

Vue.js

Nuxt.js

Certifications

2021-02 Full-stack Web developer

2022-01 LFD – Laravel full-stack developer

References

Ibidapo Adeolu.

Webastry Designs, 34 Shettima Alli Monguno Crescent, Utako District, FCT Abuja Nigeria.

Contact: +2349034884805

Mrs. Angelu Yu.

The London app brewery, 69-89 Mile End Rd, London, E1 4TT, GB, Contact: @appBrewery

Paul White

Bex-it Digital Solutions, No 9 Star Lake Close, Maitama, FCT Abuja Nigeria.

Contact: paul@bexit.com.ng